Railroad Operating Craft Journals 6427 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Railroad Operating Craft Journals
1899-1903
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers
Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen
6427 PUBS
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Publications.
Late 19th and early 20th century issues of journals published for locomotive engineers and firemen by their respective unions.
9629415
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, August 19, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 19, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5087: U.S. National Mediation Board Records Regarding Eastern, Western, and Southeastern Carriers' Conference Committee and the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers 5088: U.S. National Mediation Board Records Regarding Eastern, Western, and Southeastern Carriers' Conference Committee and the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers 5141: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Records 5141 G: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Graphics 5141 MB: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Memorabilia 5141 P: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Photographs 5147: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers Records 5176: Grand Lodge of the Ladies Society of the Former Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Records 5467: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Local 807 (Auburn, NY) Records 5475: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen General Chairman, Boston and Maine Railroad Records 5611: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Honorary Register of Disabled 5646: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Additional Records 5869: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Local 807 (Auburn, NY) Additional Records 6146 P: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen Photographs 6176: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Additional Records 6420 MB: Charles L. Peed Collection of Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Memorabilia
Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers; Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen
9629415
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1899 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1899; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Author: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers
    Notes: v.26:no.5 (1899: May)
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1902; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1902; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.36:no.8 (1902: Aug.)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1903; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1903; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.37:no.1 (1903: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1903; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.37:no.3 (1903: Mar.)
  - Item 3: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1903; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.37:no.5 (1903: May)
- Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1899; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1899; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen
    Notes: v.26:no.6 (1899: June)
  - Item 2: Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1899; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.27:no.5 (1899: Nov.)
- Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1901; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1901; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.4 (1901: Apr.)
  - Item 2: Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1901; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.31:no.1 (1901: July)
- Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1902; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1902; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.4 (1902: Apr.)
  - Item 2: Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1902; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.32:no.5 (1902: May)
  - Item 3: Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1902; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.33:no.1 (1902: July)
  - Item 4: Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1902; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.33:no.3 (1902: Sept.)
- Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1903; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1903; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.34:no.5 (1903: May)
  - Item 2: Locomotive Firemen's Magazine, 1903; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.35:no.1 (1903: July)
- The Strand Magazine, 1899; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Strand Magazine, 1899; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: George Newnes
    Notes: v.18:no.105 (1899: Oct.)